hey guys in this video we're going to
take a look at how you can change the
default folder for the notes widget on
your iphone 12 or iphone 12 pro
so on my home screen you can see i
already have a notes widget
and to change the default folder all you
have to do is touch and hold on the
widget
and then tap on edit widget
next tap on the folder icon on the right
hand side
and from the list you could choose a
different folder so let's say i want to
display all my icloud notes and select
oi cloud folder
and then tap outside the box here to
save the changes
and that's it so now i can view all my
notes in the icloud notes folder
and that's it thank you for watching
this video please subscribe to my
channel for more videos
now if you do not know how to add the
widget to the home screen this is what
you have to do just touch and hold on
the home screen then tap on the add
button
next go down
and tap on notes
and then in here you can
touch and hold onto your widget and then
drag it to the home screen
and that's it that's how you can add the
widget to your home screen thank you for
watching this video please subscribe to
my channel for more videos